Ubu Repertory Theater Script Collection ca. 1982-1994 MSS 120 MSS.120
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: French Manuscripts
  - Quintal, Patrick. 'Cent pour cent humain', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 727)
  - Rabiller, Thierry. 'L'allemand dans le placard', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 728)
  - Rafenomanjato, Charlotte. 'La paix du purgatoire', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 729)
  - Rafenomanjato, Charlotte. 'Le troupeau', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 730)
  - Raharimanana, Jean-Luc. 'Le proph et le prdent', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 731)
  - Rakotoson, Mich. 'L'histoire de koto', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 732)
  - Rakotoson, Mich. 'Un jour ma mire', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 733)
  - Rakotoson, Mich. 'La maison morte', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 734)
  - Rakotoson, Mich. 'Sambany', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 735)
  - Rakotoson, Mich. 'Si on dansait', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 736)
  - Rampal, Jacques. 'La trompette', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 737)
  - Rault, Antoine. 'La premi t', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 738)
  - Rault, Antoine. 'Dnire ou la femme d'Hercule', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 739)
  - Recoing, Jacqueline and Jean. 'Pique nique au bord du Styx', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 740)
  - Redonnet, Marie. 'Le cirque pandor', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 741)
  - Redonnet, Marie. 'Mobie Diq', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 742)
  - Reinart, Jean. 'Oniroplasmie', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 743)
  - Renauld, Sophie. 'Roman thral', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 744)
  - Renault, Jean. 'Aphrodisiaque', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 745)
  - Renault, Jean. 'Chlo/unittitle>, undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 746)
  - Repago, Gomeyo. 'Le dossier', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 747)
  - Ressi, Mich. 'La part du r', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 748)
  - Retamal, Miguel. 'La espera ou l'attente', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 749)
  - Reynaud, Yves. 'L'arbre aux oiseaux', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 750)
  - Reynaud, Yves. 'ments regrettables', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 751)
  - Reynaud, Yves. 'Prratifs de bapt a campagne', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 752)
  - Reynaud, Yves. 'Rosebottom', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 753)
  - Reza, Yasmina. 'Conversations aprun enterrement', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 754)
  - Rezvani, Serge. 'Na', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 755)
  - Richard, Joel. 'Drt', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 756)
  - Richard, Joel. 'Josette', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 757)
  - Rivi, Jean-Loup. 'Palerme ou Jsalem', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 758)
  - Rivi, Jean-Loup. 'La pi du sirocco', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 759)
  - Robbe, Frric. 'Le balcon d'un soir', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 760)
  - Robbe, Frric. 'Le balcon d'un soir', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 761)
  - Robert, Franse. 'Il y a des milliers d'oiseaux dans les arbres', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 762)
  - Robert, Franse. 'Tu connais Michel-Ange?', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 763)
  - Robin, Muriel and Palmade, Pierre. 'Ils s'aiment', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 764)
  - Roffinella, Martine. 'L'indse', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 765)
  - Rogations, Pascal. 'La derni farce de Goldoni', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 766)
  - Roger, Marc. 'Le fonctionnaire des ocs', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 767)
  - Roger, Marc. 'Janus', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 768)
  - Roland, Eve. 'La fordes jours', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 769)
  - Roland, Eve. 'Le petit chaperon rouge ou une nuit okyo', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 770)
  - Roland, Eve. 'Un de trop', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 771)
  - Rolland, Dominique. 'Les mots indigenes', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 772)
  - Rolland, Dominique. 'L'h des s errantes', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 773)
  - Ronfard, Jean-Pierre. 'Inceste', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 774)
  - Rosenfeld, Alain. 'Trente-cinq amants sur chaque collier', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 775)
  - Rossett, Alan. 'Annie, Bettie, et cetera', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 776)
  - Rossett, Alan. 'Chat qui peut', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 777)
  - Rossett, Alan. 'Un compte er', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 778)
  - Rouabhi, Mohamed. 'Les acharn, undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 779)
  - Rouabhi, Mohamed. 'De plein fouet', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 780)
  - Rouchy, Stane. 'Trois dans un bureau', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 781)
  - Rouchy, Stane. 'La grosit/unittitle>, undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 782)
  - Rouchy, Stane. 'Les assassins', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 783)
  - Roussel, Raymond. 'La poussi de soleils', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 784)
  - Roy, Marie-Thse. 'L'ivresse des profondeurs', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 785)
  - RozPascale. 'Papa Dumouriez', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 786)
  - RozPascale. 'Sainte-Icarie', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 787)
  - [Various authors]. 'Rwanda 1994 (Season 1999/2000 and 2000/2001)', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 788)
  - [Various authors]. 'Rwanda 1994 (March 2000)', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 789)
  - Sabres, Philippe. 'Le fils de Kennedy', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 790)
  - Sabrou, Frric. 'Les petites voitures', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 791)
  - Sadeghi, Nazli. 'La soeur', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 792)
  - Saget, Florence. 'Tic-tac parisienne', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 793)
  - Sagnis, Lucette. 'Le testement du jour', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 794)
  - Sagnis, Lucette-Marie. 'Les teinturiers de la lune', undated; 31142040610399 (Box I.20, Folder 795)
  - Saint-Eloy, Luc. 'Trottoir chagrin', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 796)
  - Saint-Eloy, Luc. 'Trottoir chagrin', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 797)
  - Saint-Eloy, Luc. 'Trottoir chagrin', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 798)
  - Salinger, Benjamin. 'Reflexions II', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 799)
  - Salmon, Frans. 'L'arrache', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 800)
  - Sane, Lamine. 'Kansalla Tata sacrt cite gloire', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 801)
  - SangarTiro. 'Le tournant', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 802)
  - Santiago, Jo. 'Mon nom est gravans le clair-obscur', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 803)
  - Santos-Leite, Carlos Eduardo. 'Cheetah', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 804)
  - Santos-Leite, Carlos Eduardo. 'Jonas', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 805)
  - Sarrazac, Jean-Pierre. 'Harriet', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 806)
  - Sauboua, Philippe. 'L'impromtu de la barthelasse', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 807)
  - Sauvard, Jocelyne. 'Chambre noire', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 808)
  - Sauvard, Jocelyne. 'Mater/unittitle>, undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 809)
  - Sbouai, Ta 'Le r suspendu', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 810)
  - Scarton-Kim, Katia. 'La naine blanche', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 811)
  - Schaeffer, Emmanuel. 'Comment rendre l'autre fou', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 812)
  - Schmitt, Eric-Emmanuel. 'Le visiteur', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 813)
  - Schreiber, Boris. 'Demain', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 814)
  - Schwartz-Bart, Andrt Simone. 'Un plat de porc aux bananes vertes', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 815)
  - Sebbar, Leila. 'Au fr bien-aim/unittitle>, undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 816)
  - Sebbar, Leila. 'Rue des iris', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 817)
  - Sebbar, Leila. 'Les yeux de ma m', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 818)
  - Seck, Baye Ibou. 'Le mariage de la princesse Netu', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 819)
  - Segal, Gilles. 'Le marionettiste de Lodz', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 820)
  - Sergent-Avenas, Brigitte. 'Look en stock', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 821)
  - Sevilla, Miguel Angel. 'La traversou l'archange n'est plus l/unittitle>, undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 822)
  - Shahryari, Kazem. 'Sans la voie lact, undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 823)
  - Shelley, Guy. 'Les vies anteurs', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 824)
  - Sigal, Mich. 'Gnies', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 825)
  - Sigee, Jeanne. 'La poix', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 826)
  - Simean, Christian. 'Hyenes', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 827)
  - Simean, Christian. 'Hecate', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 828)
  - Simon, Christine. 'Bestiaires', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 829)
  - Simon, Daniel. 'Snipers', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 830)
  - Simon, Jean-Yves. 'Bonsoir, Monsieur Williams', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 831)
  - Sirjacq, Louis-Charles. 'L'hiver, chapitre un', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 832)
  - Sirota, Camille Henri. 'Hector et Alice', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 833)
  - Sivadier, Jean-Frans. 'La reprise de dribbles', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 834)
  - Soulier, Daniel. 'Aprl'amour', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 835)
  - Soussigne, Jean-Pierre. 'Shipwreck', undated; 31142040610407 (Box I.21, Folder 836)
  - Souviraa, Bernard. 'La baie des sirs noy', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 837)
  - Souviraa, Bernard. 'La langue des chiens', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 838)
  - Spiegelman, Carl-Philip Emanuel. La villegiature de Konrad Dominic ort Elizabeth', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 839)
  - Steinbach, Daniel. 'Eh, l'artist, ta pillule!', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 840)
  - Steinbach, Daniel. 'L'enfant prochain', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 841)
  - Steinbach, Daniel. 'Au nom de l'homme', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 842)
  - Steinbach, Daniel. 'Quelques instants apr, undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 843)
  - Steinbach, Daniel. 'La tapette ouches', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 844)
  - Stierling, Charles. 'Clytemnestre', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 845)
  - Stiff, Vale and Carre, Frans. 'Au bout du conte', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 846)
  - Strauss, Botho. 'Le temps et al chambre', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 847)
  - Strauss, Botho. 'Le temps et la chambre [misc.]', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 848)
  - Sworzen, Marian. 'D'en bas de la guillotine dor, undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 849)
  - Szwajcer, Bruno. 'Rlution', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 850)
  - Tanase, Virgil. 'Cet enfant d'un sie colossal', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 851)
  - Tansi, Sony Labou. 'Les enfants du champignon', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 852)
  - Tansi, Sony Labou. 'Moi, venue de l'empire', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 853)
  - Tardieu, Jean. 'Le rite du premier soir', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 854)
  - Tardieu, Jean. 'La citans sommeil', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 855)
  - Tartar, Luc. 'Les arabes oitiers', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 856)
  - Tedondje, Alexis Blaise. 'Qui succra donc kem-Nembou?', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 857)
  - Terrasson, Paul. 'Samba', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 858)
  - Theron, Anne. 'Notre e de mis', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 859)
  - Theron, Anne. 'Villa nova de Milfontes', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 860)
  - Tholy, RenAntipolis [modified version of Buroctopus or Les bureaux tenticulaires]', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 861)
  - Tholy, Ren'Grave, mais non dspe', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 862)
  - Thomas, Philippe. 'Oh, papa!', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 863)
  - Thomas, Philippe. 'La vie d'artiste', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 864)
  - Tomazyk, Olivier. 'Les figures', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 865)
  - Tournier, Michel. 'Le fetichiste', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 866)
  - Tremblay, Larry. 'Le ge de la rue Drolet', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 867)
  - Tristan, Frrick. 'Chambre noire', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 868)
  - Troman, Morley. 'La reine d'Ecosse n'est pas une femme', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 869)
  - Tsibinda, Marie-Ltine. 'Tarentelle tropicale', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 870)
  - Turp, Gilbert. 'Les fant de Martin', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 871)
  - Turp, Gilbert. 'La barbe de BB', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 872)
  - Turp, Gilbert. 'Les cauchmars du grand monde', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 873)
  - Valentin, Dominique. 'Le dernier voyage', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 874)
  - Valletti, Serge. 'Cinq duo', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 875)
  - Valmont, Mona. 'Le sang pur', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 876)
  - Van Belle, Anita and Delperdange, Patrick. 'Nuit d'amour', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 877)
  - Vanhalt, Christophe. 'Le fauteuil de Bnice', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 878)
  - Van Westrenen, Pieter Anton. 'Mondrian..?', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 879)
  - Van Westrenen, Pieter Anton. 'Quand tomberont les branches', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 880)
  - Vautrin, Jean. 'Baby Boom', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 881)
  - Veber, Francis. 'L'enlment', undated; 31142040610415 (Box I.22, Folder 882)
  - Vinaver, Michel. 'L'ssion de tvision', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 883)
  - Vinaver, Michel. '[a letter and promo packet to F. Kourilsky and K. Beattie]', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 884)
  - [Various Authors]. 'Vingt-deux les pis I', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 885)
  - [Various Authors]. 'Vingt-deux les pis II', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 886)
  - Visdei, Anca. 'Histoire d'amour ou la vie, l'amour, le piano', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 887)
  - Visdei, Anca. 'Ma Callas', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 888)
  - Visdei, Anca. 'Nous sommes toutes des femmes roumaines', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 889)
  - Visdei, Anca and Ducceschi, Maria. 'Les ppatciens', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 890)
  - Visdei, Anca. 'Photo de classe', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 891)
  - Visdei, Anca. 'Toujours ensemble', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 892)
  - Visniec, Mat L'histoire des ours panda racontpar un saxophoniste qui a une petite amie rancfort', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 893)
  - Visniec, Mat 'L'homme poubelle', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 894)
  - Visniec, Mat Du sexe la femme comme champ de bataille dans la guerre en Bosnie', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 895)
  - Vu, Khac Khoan. 'Genghis Khan', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 896)
  - Vuillermoz, Jean-Louis. 'Le bord du monde', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 897)
  - Vuillermoz, Jean-Louis. 'Memores', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 898)
  - Vuillermoz, Jean-Louis. 'Le vol de l'ombre', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 899)
  - Walter, Ariane. 'Rimbe et Lan', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 900)
  - Waters, Chris. 'Interdit', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 901)
  - Weber, Thomas. 'La fille evolu, undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 902)
  - Weingarten, Romain. 'L'', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 903)
  - Weingarten, Romain. 'Neige', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 904)
  - Wenzel, Jean-Paul. 'Doublages', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 905)
  - Wenzel, Jean-Paul. 'Simple retour', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 906)
  - Wilson, Dave. 'Un citoyen gralement perplex/unittitle>, undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 907)
  - Wittig, Monique. 'Le voyage sans fin', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 908)
  - Worms, Jeannine. 'Un air pur', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 909)
  - Worms, Jeannine. 'Avec ou sans arbres', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 910)
  - Worms, Jeannine. 'Pardon monsieur', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 911)
  - Worms, Jeannine. 'La recette', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 912)
  - Xingjian, Gao. 'Au bord de la vie', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 913)
  - Xingjian, Gao. 'Quatre quatuors pour le week-end', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 914)
  - Xingjian, Gao. 'Le somnambule', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 915)
  - Yacine, Kateb. 'Le bourgeois sans-culotte ou le spectre du parc morceau', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 916)
  - Yacine, Kateb. 'Palestine trahie', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 917)
  - Yacoub, Abdellatif. 'Ahmed bouffe tout la gamelle et les fourchettes avec', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 918)
  - Yanni, Nicole. 'Le retrait', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 919)
  - Yoann, Patrick. 'Le mal de mer', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 920)
  - Yoka, Lye Mudaba. 'La foire des pharaons', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 921)
  - Zadi Zaourou, Bottey. 'La guerre des femmes', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 922)
  - Zadi Zaourou, Bottey. 'La guerre des femmes', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 923)
  - Zambon, Catherine. 'Catarineto, la nuit de la Saint Jean', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 924)
  - Zilberstein, Guy. 'Davenport Swing', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 925)
  - Zinzou, Suro Agbota. 'La tortue philosophe', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 926)
  - Zinzou, Suro Agbota. 'Y et le mais du roi', undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 927)
  - [Unknown fragment], undated; 31142040610423 (Box I.23, Folder 928)
- Series II: English Manuscripts
  - Adamov, Arthur. 'All Against All', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 1)
  - Adamov, Arthur. 'Dead Souls', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 2)
  - Adamov, Arthur. 'Ping-Pong', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 3)
  - Adamov, Arthur. 'Ping Pong', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 4)
  - Adamov, Arthur. 'Professor Taranne', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 5)
  - Adamov, Arthur. 'Recollections', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 6)
  - Adamov, Arthur. 'A Refuse Problem', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 7)
  - Adamov, Arthur. 'Spring 71', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 8)
  - Affinito, Alfonso. 'Vie de Boheme', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 9)
  - D'Aguila, Carlos and Marais, Claude. 'The Carpenter's House', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 10)
  - Alkemade, Philippe. 'The Blue Trees', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 11)
  - Alkemade, Philippe. 'Hope Street (Today)', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 12)
  - Alkemade, Philippe. 'Strange How the Same Things Make Us Laugh and Cry', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 13)
  - Amacker, Jonathan. '(adaptor). Half a Dozen Roses', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 14)
  - Anouilh, Jean. Dear Antoine', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 15)
  - Anouilh, Jean. 'Ornifle', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 16)
  - Anouilh, Jean. 'Romeo and Jeannette', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 17)
  - Anouilh, Jean. 'Thomas More', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 18)
  - Apostolides, Jean-Marie. 'Through One Eye Darkly', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 19)
  - Apostolides, Jean-Marie. 'Waiting for Beckett', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 20)
  - Aron, Jean-Paul. 'Pulling Punches', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 21)
  - Asseng, Protais. 'Enough Is Enough', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 22)
  - Atlan, Liliane. 'The Passerby', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 23)
  - Audiberti, Jacques. 'Quoat-Quoat', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 24)
  - Avron, Philippe. 'Avron Big Bang', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 25)
  - Avron, Philippe. 'I Am a Salmon', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 26)
  - Bacon, Jean. 'If Madame Permits', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 27)
  - Barillet, Pierre. 'Gustave and Louise', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 28)
  - Ballini, Georges. 'By Toutalis! The Sky's About to Fall on Our Heads!', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 29)
  - Barrette, Jacqueline. 'Stolen Tears', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 30)
  - Bart, Reine. 'Alive by Night', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 31)
  - Bauby, Jean-Dominique. 'The Diving Bell and the Butterfly', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 32)
  - Bauer, Jean-Louis. 'The Two Jules', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 33)
  - Brd, Christian. 'Butterball', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 34)
  - Bensoussan, Georges. 'East West or The Paths of Exile', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 35)
  - Bergeron, Jean-Pierre. 'Macho Man', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 36)
  - BerthommLuce and Le Guillochet, Christian. 'The Wedding', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 37)
  - Bertin, Charles. 'Christopher Columbus', undated; 31142040610431 (Box II.1, Folder 38)
  - Besnehard, Daniel. 'The Child in Obock', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 39)
  - Besnehard, Daniel. 'Companion Pieces', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 40)
  - Besnehard, Daniel. 'Hudson River: A Longing for Exile', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 41)
  - Besset, Jean-Marie. 'A Commentary on Love', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 42)
  - Besset, Jean-Marie. 'A Foreign Fair', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 43)
  - Besset, Jean-Marie. 'The Function', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 44)
  - Besset, Jean-Marie. 'Marie Hasparren', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 45)
  - Besset, Jean-Marie. 'Villa Luco', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 46)
  - Bielski, Nella and Berger, John. 'A Room for Sacha or Lessons in Geography', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 47)
  - [Unknown author]. 'Big-time Life', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 48)
  - Blais, Marie-Claire. A Clash of Symbols', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 48a.)
  - Blanchot, Maurice. 'The Madness of the Day', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 49)
  - Bonal, Denise. 'In Transit', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 50)
  - Bopoungo, Jean Carltetto. 'The Secret of Immortals', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 51)
  - Bosquet, Alain. 'An Inmate at Auschwitz', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 52)
  - Bouchard, Michel Marc. 'The Coronation Voyage', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 53)
  - Bouchard, Jean. 'Is That How It Was?', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 54)
  - Boucher, Denise. 'When Faeries Thirst', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 55)
  - Boulva, Josette and Gatard, Marie. 'My Dear Rose', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 56)
  - Bourdet, Edouard. 'La Cr de la Cr', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 57)